Roxane Connick Carlisle collection
American Folklife Center, Library of Congress
- Series 3: Photographs, Due to the small space in which to write on the slide mats, some of the information is unclear or difficult to understand. Carlisle's spelling of proper names of locations or ethnic groups reflect contemporary spelling. In these cases, the first instance is revised to reflec
  - Subseries 11: Roxane in Omdurman and Khartoum, Republic of Sudan 1963 - with Sudanese friends Abdel Karim el Kably, Mahi Ismail, Carol Jackson, and Mogran tea party with Bakhita Amin, Mahaesin Shorbagi; views of Mogran
    - My bed at Hai el Matar house, 1 slide: color, Kodachrome II; 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH0667 (Box 9)
    - House at Hai el Matar; my equipment, 1 slide: color, Kodachrome II; 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH0668 (Box 9)
    - Roxane, soldier and radio truck; Omdurman, July 1963, 1 slide: color, Kodachrome II; 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH0669 (Box 9)
    - Roxane, soldier, radio truck, July 1963, 1 slide: color, Kodachrome II; 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH0670 (Box 9)
    - Roxane and friend before broadcasting station in Omdurman, July 1963, 1 slide: color, Kodachrome II; 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH0671 (Box 9)
    - Roxane with librarian of broadcasting station in Omdurman, July 1963, 1 slide: color, Kodachrome II; 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH0672 (Box 9)
    - Roxane and tailor near the Amins; Omdurman, July 1963, 1 slide: color, Kodachrome II; 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH0673 (Box 9)
    - Roxane with Omdurman tailor, July 1963, 1 slide: color, Kodachrome II; 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH0674 (Box 9)
    - Roxane and mahdi's tomb; Omdurman, July 1963, 1 slide: color, Kodachrome II; 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH0675 (Box 9)
    - Roxane with Osman Hussein before Mahdi's tomb, 1 slide: color, Kodachrome II; 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH0676 (Box 9)
    - Roxane with Osman Hussein in front of Mahdi's tomb, July 1963, 1 slide: color, Kodachrome II; 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH0677 (Box 9)
    - Information Ministry photographer on Mogren Bridge, July 1963, 1 slide: color, Kodachrome II; 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH0678 (Box 9)
    - Roxane on Mogren bridge, July 1963, 1 slide: color, Kodachrome II; 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH0679 (Box 9)
    - Roxane on bridge and Mogren, July 1963, 1 slide: color, Kodachrome II; 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH0680 (Box 9)
    - Roxane on Mogren bridge, July 1963, 1 slide: color, Kodachrome II; 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH0681 (Box 9)
    - Roxane with sanitation inspector along the Nile; Khartoum, July 1963, 1 slide: color, Kodachrome II; 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH0682 (Box 9)
    - Roxane with sanitation inspector along Nile river; Khartoum, July 1963, 1 slide: color, Kodachrome II; 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH0683 (Box 9)
    - Roxane and ox at Nile waterwheel: Khartoum, July 1963, 1 slide: color, Kodachrome II; 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH0684 (Box 9)
    - Roxane at Nile waterwheel; Khartoum, July 1963, 1 slide: color, Kodachrome II; 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH0685 (Box 9)
    - Roxane before Egyptian mosque; Khartoum, July 1963, 1 slide: color, Kodachrome II; 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH0686 (Box 9)
    - American Embassy; Khartoum, July 1963, 1 slide: color, Kodachrome II; 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH0687 (Box 9)
    - Before the new Sudan Hotel in Khartoum, July 1963, 1 slide: color, Kodachrome II; 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH0688 (Box 9)
    - Before the new Sudan Hotel in Khartoum, July 1963, 1 slide: color, Kodachrome II; 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH0689 (Box 9)
    - Roxane and Palace guard; Khartoum, July 1963, 1 slide: color, Kodachrome II; 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH0690 (Box 9)
    - On Palace steps; Khartoum, July 1963, 1 slide: color, Kodachrome II; 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH0691 (Box 9)
    - Roxane McCollester on steps of Palace; Khartoum, Sudan, 1 slide: color, Kodachrome II; 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH0692 (Box 9)
    - Roxane and Bakhita along Nile in Omdurman, August 1963, 1 slide: color, Kodachrome II; 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH0693 (Box 9)
    - Roxane and Bakhita Amin along Nile in Omdurman, August 1963, 1 slide: color, Kodachrome II; 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH0694 (Box 9)
    - Roxane point to Nile riverboats; Omdurman, July 1963, 1 slide: color, Kodachrome II; 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH0695 (Box 9)
    - Me before Amin house; Omdurman, August 1963, 1 slide: color, Kodachrome II; 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH0696 (Box 9)
    - Roxane in front of Amin house, 1 slide: color, Kodachrome II; 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH0697 (Box 9)
    - Roxane McCollester in Amin Compound; Omdurman, 1963, 1 slide: color, Kodachrome; 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH0698 (Box 9)
    - Me in tob with Yahia girls; Omdurman, August 1963, 1 slide: color, Kodachrome II; 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH0699 (Box 9)
    - Roxane McCollester in Amin compound; Omdurman, 1963, 1 slide: color, Kodachrome; 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH0700 (Box 9)
    - Naima Yahia and Roxane in tob at Yahia house, 1 slide: color, Kodachrome II; 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH0701 (Box 9)
    - Roxane pounding dura in Yahia compound, Omdurman, August 1963, 1 slide: color, Kodachrome II; 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH0702 (Box 9)
    - Roxane and bridal crown at Sakina Yahia's wedding; Omdurman, August 1963, 1 slide: color, Kodachrome II; 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH0703 (Box 9)
    - Roxane in Saadig's garden, 1 slide: color, Kodachrome II; 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH0704 (Box 9)
    - Roxane writing on Saadig terrace, 1 slide: color, Kodachrome II; 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH0705 (Box 9)
    - Roxane writing in Saadig's garden, 1 slide: color, Kodachrome II; 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH0706 (Box 9)
    - Roxane and her ud; Jackson house, Mogren; Khartoum, September 6, 1963, 1 slide: color, Kodachrome II; 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH0707 (Box 9)
    - Roxane with ud; Jackson home, Mogren; Khartoum, September 6, 1963, 1 slide: color, Kodachrome II; 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH0708 (Box 9)
    - Roxane and ud; Jackson house in Khartoum, September 6, 1963, 1 slide: color, Kodachrome II; 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH0709 (Box 9)
    - Roxane at Jackson home in Mogren, Khartoum; just before take-off at airport, September 6, 1963, 1 slide: color, Kodachrome II; 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH0710 (Box 9)
    - Carol Jackson at home; Mogren Khartoum, September 6, 1963, 1 slide: color, Kodachrome II; 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH0711 (Box 9)
    - Mrs. Robert Jackson (Carol) at her home in Mogren Khartoum, September 6, 1963, 1 slide: color, Kodachrome II; 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH0712 (Box 9)
    - Carol Jackson at home - Mogren; Khartoum, September 6, 1963, 1 slide: color, Kodachrome II; 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH0713 (Box 9)
    - Carol Jackson at home - Mogren; Khartoum, September 6, 1963, 1 slide: color, Kodachrome II; 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH0714 (Box 9)
    - Carol Jackson and my ud; Khartoum, September 6, 1963, 1 slide: color, Kodachrome II; 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH0715 (Box 9)
    - Carol Jackson; Khartoum, September 6, 1963, 1 slide: color, Kodachrome II; 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH0716 (Box 9)
    - Table set for my tea party in Mogren, August 1963, 1 slide: color, Kodachrome II; 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH0717 (Box 9)
    - Debby Jackson running into house, Mogren, August 1963, 1 slide: color, Kodachrome II; 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH0718 (Box 9)
    - Debby Jackson 's cake for my tea party, Mogren, August 1963, 1 slide: color, Kodachrome II; 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH0719 (Box 9)
    - Ladies at the tea party, with cake in foreground, 1 slide: color, Kodachrome II; 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH0720 (Box 9)
    - Ahmed and guests at my tea party in Mogren house, August 1963, 1 slide: color, Kodachrome II; 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH0721 (Box 9)
    - Ladies at the tea party, with cake in foreground, 1 slide: color, Kodachrome II; 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH0722 (Box 9)
    - Ladies at the tea party, with cake in foreground, 1 slide: color, Kodachrome II; 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH0723 (Box 9)
    - Ladies at the tea party, 1 slide: color, Kodachrome II; 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH0724 (Box 9)
    - Mahaesin Sharleagi and Maima Bukra, at the tea party, 1 slide: color, Kodachrome II; 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH0725 (Box 9)
    - Mahaesin, at the tea party, 1 slide: color, Kodachrome II; 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH0726 (Box 9)
    - Mahaesin Sharleagi, Maima Bukra, Bakhita Amin, at the tea party, 1 slide: color, Kodachrome II; 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH0727 (Box 9)
    - Mahaesin Sharleagi, Maima Bukra, Bakhita Amin, and Medina Babbiker el Galli, at the tea party, 1 slide: color, Kodachrome II; 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH0728 (Box 9)
    - Medina Babbiker el Galli; tea party, Mogren, Khartoum, 1 slide: color, Kodachrome II; 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH0729 (Box 9)
    - Mahaesin Sharleagi and Maima Bukra, at the tea party, 1 slide: color, Kodachrome II; 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH0730 (Box 9)
    - Naima el Bakra, 1 slide: color, Kodachrome II; 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH0731 (Box 9)
    - Makaesin Shorlagi Magrem at Jackson house, August 1963, 1 slide: color, Kodachrome II; 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH0732 (Box 9)
    - el Kably laughing, 1 slide: color, Kodachrome II; 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH0733 (Box 9)
    - Mahi Ismail in Mai el Mater house, 1 slide: color, Kodachrome II; 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH0734 (Box 9)
    - Mahi Ismail, 1 slide: color, Kodachrome II; 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH0735 (Box 9)
    - Mahi Ismail, 1 slide: color, Kodachrome II; 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH0736 (Box 9)
  - Subseries 12: Upper Nile Province - Sudan, April 1963; general views of Akobo and Anuak settlements in vicinity with some singers and musicians
    - Convoy bogged down on a road to Akobo, Upper Nile Province, April 1963, 1 slide: color, Kodachrome; 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH0737 (Box 9)
    - Road to Akobo, Upper Nile Province, April 1963, 1 slide: color, Kodachrome; 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH0738 (Box 9)
    - Birds caught along road to Akobo, Upper Nile Province, April 1963, 1 slide: color, Kodachrome; 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH0739 (Box 9)
    - Akobo, Upper Nile Province, 1 slide: color, Kodachrome; 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH0740 (Box 9)
    - Akobo rest house; Upper Nile Province, April 1963, 1 slide: color, Kodachrome; 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH0741 (Box 9)
    - Akobo, Upper Nile Province, 1 slide: color, Kodachrome; 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH0742 (Box 9)
    - Garden of town administrator's home; Akobo, Upper Nile Province, April 1963, 1 slide: color, Kodachrome; 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH0743 (Box 9)
    - Akobo, Upper Nile Province, April 1963, 1 slide: color, Kodachrome; 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH0744 (Box 9)
    - Pibor River at Akobo, Upper Nile Province, April 1963, 1 slide: color, Kodachrome; 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH0745 (Box 9)
    - Water pump from Pibor River to governor's plantation in Akobo, Upper Nile Province, April 1963, 1 slide: color, Kodachrome; 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH0746 (Box 9)
    - Governor's plantation near Victor Bol's house in Akobo, Upper Nile Province, April 1963, 1 slide: color, Kodachrome; 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH0747 (Box 9)
    - Akobo, Upper Nile Province, 1 slide: color, Kodachrome; 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH0748 (Box 9)
    - Akobo, Upper Nile Province, 1 slide: color, Kodachrome; 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH0749 (Box 9)
    - Akobo, Upper Nile Province, 1 slide (duplicate): black and white; 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH0750 (Box 9)
    - Akobo - time chime; Sudan, 1 slide (duplicate): black and white; 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH0751 (Box 9)
    - Akobo - time chime and soldier; Sudan, April 1963, 1 slide: color, Kodachrome; 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH0752 (Box 9)
    - Akobo - people in the courtyard, 1 slide (duplicate): black and white; 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH0753 (Box 9)
    - Akobo - on the road, with people standing, plus two mounted police officers, 1 slide (duplicate): black and white; 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH0754 (Box 9)
    - Akobo - a mounted police officer, 1 slide (duplicate): black and white; 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH0755 (Box 9)
    - Akobo, 1 slide (duplicate): black and white; 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH0756 (Box 9)
    - Akobo, 1 slide (duplicate): black and white; 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH0757 (Box 9)
    - Akobo, 1 slide (duplicate): black and white; 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH0758 (Box 9)
    - Akobo, 1 slide (duplicate): black and white; 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH0759 (Box 9)
    - Akobo - pounding dura, 1 slide (duplicate): black and white; 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH0760 (Box 9)
    - Akobo - pounding dura, 1 slide (duplicate): black and white; 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH0761 (Box 9)
    - Akobo - pounding dura, 1 slide (duplicate): black and white; 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH0762 (Box 9)
    - Pounding dura in Victor Bol's yard and donkey delivering water, 1 slide: color, Kodachrome; 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH0763 (Box 9)
    - Donkeys and people, 1 slide (duplicate): black and white; 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH0764 (Box 9)
    - Donkeys and people, 1 slide (duplicate): black and white; 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH0765 (Box 9)
    - Victor Bol in governor's plantation garden with overseer, water carrier, irrigation ditch, 1 slide: color, Kodachrome; 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH0766 (Box 9)
    - Victor Bol, wife and children; Akobo, Upper Nile Province, April 1963, 1 slide: color, Kodachrome; 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH0767 (Box 9)
    - Akobo - two children, playing, 1 slide (duplicate): black and white; 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH0768 (Box 9)
    - Victor Bol, wife and children; Akobo, Upper Nile Province; background woman pounding dura, 1 slide: color, Kodachrome; 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH0769 (Box 9)
    - Victor Bol, Dinka; town administrator, Akobo, April 1963, 1 slide: color, Kodachrome; 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH0770 (Box 9)
    - Victor Bol, Dinka; town administrator, Akobo, April 1963, 1 slide: color, Kodachrome; 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH0771 (Box 9)
    - Administration hut and square in Akobo, Upper Nile Province, April 1963, 1 slide: color, Kodachrome; 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH0772 (Box 9)
    - Roxane (left), Uthiri Juok (right) and son (center); Akobo area, Upper Nile Province; Sudan, 1963, 1 slide (duplicate): black and white; 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH0773 (Box 9)
    - Man (smoking?), surrounded by other men, 1 slide (duplicate): black and white; 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH0774 (Box 9)
    - Man (smoking?), surrounded by other men, 1 slide (duplicate): black and white; 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH0775 (Box 9)
    - Three men, 1 slide (duplicate): black and white; 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH0776 (Box 9)
    - Three men; several people in the background, 1 slide (duplicate): black and white; 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH0777 (Box 9)
    - Three men, in profile, 1 slide (duplicate): black and white; 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH0778 (Box 9)
    - Man sitting in foreground; musicians in the background, 1 slide (duplicate): black and white; 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH0779 (Box 9)
    - Man sitting in foreground; musicians in the background, 1 slide (duplicate): black and white; 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH0780 (Box 9)
    - Man sitting in foreground; musicians in the background, 1 slide (duplicate): black and white; 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH0781 (Box 9)
    - Man, in profile, 1 slide (duplicate): black and white; 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH0782 (Box 9)
    - Man, in profile, 1 slide (duplicate): black and white; 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH0783 (Box 9)
    - Man, in profile, 1 slide (duplicate): black and white; 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH0784 (Box 9)
    - Anuak woman (standing) and aguaga rattle; Upper Nile Province, Sudan, 1963, 1 slide (duplicate): black and white; 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH0785 (Box 9)
    - Anuak woman (seated); Upper Nile Province, Sudan, 1963, 1 slide (duplicate): black and white; 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH0786 (Box 9)
    - Anuak drums; Akobo area; Upper Nile Province, Sudan, 1963, 1 slide (duplicate): black and white; 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH0787 (Box 9)
    - Anuak drums; Akobo area; Upper Nile Province, Sudan, 1963, 1 slide (duplicate): black and white; 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH0788 (Box 9)
      A 7-inch audio tape box is leaning against one drum.
    - Man playing a small flute, 1 slide (duplicate): black and white; 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH0789 (Box 9)
    - Man playing a small flute, 1 slide (duplicate): black and white; 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH0790 (Box 9)
    - Nuer woman singer, Akobo, Upper Nile Province, April 1963, 1 slide: color, Kodachrome; 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH0791 (Box 9)
    - View of Upper Nile Province from Cessna flying me out of Akobo to Malakal, 1 slide: color, Kodachrome; 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH0792 (Box 9)
    - View of Upper Nile Province from Cessna talking me to Malakal, April 1963, 1 slide: color, Kodachrome; 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH0793 (Box 9)
    - Pilot Jacobeen flying me out of Akobo in Cessna, April 1963, 1 slide: color, Kodachrome; 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH0794 (Box 9)
    - View of Upper Nile Province on route to Malakal from Akobo, April 1963, 1 slide: color, Kodachrome; 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH0795 (Box 9)
    - Anuak singers; Akobo, Upper Nile Province, 1 slide: color, Kodachrome; 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH0796 (Box 9)
    - Anuak singers; Akobo, Upper Nile Province, 1 slide: color, Kodachrome; 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH0797 (Box 9)
    - Anuak drummers; Akobo, Upper Nile Province, April 1963, 1 slide: color, Kodachrome; 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH0798 (Box 9)
    - Anuak; Akobo, Upper Nile Province, 1 slide: color, Kodachrome; 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH0799 (Box 9)
    - Anuak; Akobo, Upper Nile Province, 1 slide: color, Kodachrome; 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH0800 (Box 9)
    - Anuak; Akobo, Upper Nile Province, 1 slide: color, Kodachrome; 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH0801 (Box 9)
    - Gathering of people under trees, 1 photograph: black-and-white print; 2 3/4 x 2 in.; AFC 2012/008: PH0802 (Box-folder 4/1)
      Originally located with slides "Upper Nile Province - Sudan; April 1963." Now housed with PH1533-PH1544.
    - Hut, with man standing in doorway, 1 photograph: black-and-white print; 2 3/4 x 2 in.; AFC 2012/008: PH0803 (Box-folder 4/1)
    - Woman sitting at a table, 1 photograph: black-and-white print; 2 3/4 x 2 in.; AFC 2012/008: PH0804 (Box-folder 4/1)
  - Subseries 13: Upper Nile Province - Sudan, 1963; Malakal; general views of town; Governor Osman Nasr at home; District Commissioner Emin el Tinay
    - Roxane's plane for Malakal; Khartoum, April 1963, 1 slide: color, Kodachrome; 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH0805 (Box 10)
    - Nile River at Malakal; Upper Nile Province, April 1963, 1 slide: color, Kodachrome; 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH0806 (Box 10)
    - Nile at Malakal, 1 slide: color, Kodachrome; 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH0807 (Box 10)
    - Waiting for the ferry at Malakal, Upper Nile Province, April 1963, 1 slide: color, Kodachrome; 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH0808 (Box 10)
    - Nile view from province authority office, Malakal showing water hyacinths, 1963, 1 slide: color, Kodachrome; 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH0809 (Box 10)
    - Entrance of province authority offices, Malakal, 1 slide: color, Kodachrome; 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH0810 (Box 10)
    - Taha Abdel Rahman in front of offices of the province authority; Malakal, Sudan, April 1963, 1 slide: color, Kodachrome; 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH0811 (Box 10)
    - Garden of province authority offices, Malakal, 1 slide: color, Kodachrome; 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH0812 (Box 10)
    - View of Nile from garden of military governor's mansions, Malakal, 1 slide: color, Kodachrome; 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH0813 (Box 10)
    - View of Nile from garden, 1 slide (duplicate): black and white; 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH0814 (Box 10)
    - Governor's mansion, Malakal; Military governor Osman Nasr Osman, May 1963, 1 slide: color, Kodachrome; 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH0815 (Box 10)
    - View of governor's house in Malakal; Upper Nile Province, May 1963, 1 slide (duplicate): black and white; 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH0816 (Box 10)
    - Back of governor's house, facing Nile, 1 slide (duplicate): black and white; 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH0817 (Box 10)
    - Back of governor's house, facing Nile, 1 slide (duplicate): black and white; 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH0818 (Box 10)
    - Back of governor's house facing Nile and being the entrance used by important visitors, 1 slide (duplicate): black and white; 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH0819 (Box 10)
    - View of governor's house, 1 slide (duplicate): black and white; 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH0820 (Box 10)
    - View of governor's house, 1 slide (duplicate): black and white; 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH0821 (Box 10)
    - Cows under governor's mansion; Malakal, 1 slide: color, Kodachrome; 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH0822 (Box 10)
    - Cows under governor's mansion; Malakal, 1 slide (duplicate): black and white; 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH0823 (Box 10)
    - Cows under governor's mansion; Malakal, 1 slide (duplicate): black and white; 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH0824 (Box 10)
    - Goats, 1 slide (duplicate): black and white; 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH0825 (Box 10)
    - Goats in background, birds in foreground, 1 slide (duplicate): black and white; 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH0826 (Box 10)
    - Garden of governor's house; Malakal, April 1963, 1 slide: color, Kodachrome; 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH0827 (Box 10)
    - Medina, governor's wife feeding pigeons at home in Malakal, May 1963, 1 slide (duplicate): black and white; 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH0828 (Box 10)
    - Medina, governor's wife feeding pigeons at home in Malakal, May 1963, 1 slide (duplicate): black and white; 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH0829 (Box 10)
    - Governor Osman Nasr and family on a picnic near Malakal; Upper Nile Province, Sudan, May 1963, 1 slide (duplicate): black and white; 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH0830 (Box 10)
    - Governor Nasr's wife on a picnic; Sudan, May 1963, 1 slide (duplicate): black and white; 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH0831 (Box 10)
    - Governor Nasr's family on picnic outside Malakal; Sudan, May 1963, 1 slide (duplicate): black and white; 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH0832 (Box 10)
    - Malakal, Upper Nile Province, April 1963, 1 slide: color, Kodachrome II; 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH0833 (Box 10)
    - Fence around yard of Mohammed Bashir el Ahmadi's house in Malakal, April 1963, 1 slide: color, Kodachrome II; 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH0834 (Box 10)
    - Mohammed Bashir el Ahmadi's house in Malakal, April 1963, 1 slide: color, Kodachrome II; 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH0835 (Box 10)
    - Mohammed Bashir el Ahmadi's house in Malakal, April 1963, 1 slide: color, Kodachrome II; 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH0836 (Box 10)
    - House in Malakal, 1 slide: color, Kodachrome II; 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH0837 (Box 10)
    - Malakal, Upper Nile Province, April 1963, 1 slide: color, Kodachrome II; 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH0838 (Box 10)
    - Street in Kodoc; Upper Nile Province, April 1963, 1 slide: color, Kodachrome II; 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH0839 (Box 10)
    - Emin el Tinay, district commissioner of Shilluk territory; Malakal dock, 1 slide: color, Kodachrome II; 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH0840 (Box 10)
    - Sayed Emin el Tinay with his truck before leaving Kodoc for Malakal, 1 slide (duplicate): black and white; 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH0841 (Box 10)
    - Sayed Emin el Tinay with his truck before leaving Kodoc for Malakal, 1 slide (duplicate): black and white; 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH0842 (Box 10)
    - Sayed Emin el Tinay with his truck before leaving Kodoc for Malakal, April 1963, 1 slide: color, Kodachrome II; 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH0843 (Box 10)
    - Sayed Emin el Tinay; district Commissioner of Shilluk Territory; Upper Nile Province, April 1963, 1 slide: color, Ektachrome; 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH0844 (Box 10)
    - Sayed Emin el Tinay, on front steps of house, April 1963, 1 slide: color, Kodachrome II; 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH0845 (Box 10)
    - Children of Sayed Emin of Tinay at Kodoc; Upper Nile Province, Sudan, April 1963, 1 slide (duplicate): black and white; 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH0846 (Box 10)
    - Sayed el Tinay's daughter; Kodoc, Upper Nile Province, April 1963, 1 slide: color, Ektachrome; 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH0847 (Box 10)
    - Sayed el Tinay's children; Kodoc, Upper Nile Province, April 1963, 1 slide: color, Ektachrome; 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH0848 (Box 10)
    - Sayed el Tinay's daughter; Kodoc, Upper Nile Province, April 1963, 35 mm slide; color Ektachrome; AFC 2012/008: PH0849 (Box 10)